const arr = [
    {
        qid:"001",
        question:"How are _____ ?",
        op1:"I",
        op2:"you",
        op3:"me",
        op4:"he",
        ans:"you",
        difficulty:1
    },
    {
        qid:"002",
        question:"I _____ Sachin.",
        op1:"am",
        op2:"is",
        op3:"me",
        op4:"he",
        ans:"am",
        difficulty:1
    },
    {
        qid:"003",
        question:"They _____ playing.",
        op1:"is",
        op2:"you",
        op3:"are",
        op4:"do",
        ans:"are",
        difficulty:1
    },
    {
        qid:"004",
        question:"Rohan is so magnanimous that everyone is always _____ to help him in his project.",
        op1:"eager",
        op2:"enthusiastic",
        op3:"reluctant",
        op4:"ignorant",
        ans:"eager",
        difficulty:3
    },
    {
        qid:"005",
        question:"I settled ______ Canada last year.",
        op1:"at",
        op2:"in",
        op3:"off",
        op4:"on",
        ans:"in",
        difficulty:2
    },
    {
        qid:"006",
        question:"I do not know what________ my father choose that particular school.",
        op1:"happened",
        op2:"controlled",
        op3:"made",
        op4:"asked",
        ans:"made",
        difficulty:3
    },
    {
        qid:"007",
        question:"It is time you ________ home.",
        op1:"go",
        op2:"went",
        op3:"come",
        op4:"reach",
        ans:"went",
        difficulty:2
    },
    {
        qid:"008",
        question:"None of the food was wasted _______",
        op1:"wasn't",
        op2:"was it",
        op3:"were it",
        op4:"werenâ€™t",
        ans:"was it",
        difficulty:2
    },
    {
        qid:"009",
        question:"He found the jewellery box empty. All the ornaments, jewels, etc were ________",
        op1:"protected",
        op2:"seized",
        op3:"sold",
        op4:"stolen",
        ans:"stolen",
        difficulty:2
    },
    {
        qid:"010",
        question:" His arguments in the court were so ________ that he shattered the evidence built by the opposition lawyer.",
        op1:"diagnostic",
        op2:"voluminous",
        op3:"penetrative",
        op4:"worldly",
        ans:"penetrative",
        difficulty:2
    }
];

module.exports = arr;